### AYUSH GOEL

857-376-9346 | goel.ay@northeastern.edu | https://www.linkedin.com/in/ayushgoel1005/

## **SUMMARY**

Self-taught trader and investor in financial market, commodity sector (Futures) specialist and current Quantitative Finance candidate at Northeastern University. Would like to create an identity in Global Investment Research, Global Market, Real Estate, Asset & Investment Management, Equity departments.

\_\_\_\_\_

## **EDUCATION**

## Northeastern University, Boston, MA

Sept 2021 - Dec 2022

Current student of Master of Science in Quantitative Finance

Related Courses: Corporate Finance, Investment Analysis, Data Analytics in Finance, Derivatives and Risk Analytics

## Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University, India

Aug 2017 - Oct 2020

Bachelor of Commerce (Honors) (GPA- 3.97/4.00)

Related Courses: Business Statistics, Financial Modeling, Financial Accounting, Information Systems Management

## TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

Tally ERP9, R, Python, Windows, UNIX, R Programming, MATLAB, SQL, Technical & Fundamental Analysis, Power BI, Tableau, Bloomberg Terminal

**PROJECTS** 

## Evaluating the effectiveness of online advertisements on today's market

Jan 2020 - Sep 2020

The objectives of the field study are to evaluate the effectiveness and importance of online advertisements in today's market and study the satisfaction level of online viewers.

# A study on public awareness about equity and role of SEBI in Indian Stock market

Jan 2018 - May 2018

The study aimed to analyze the size of the market which invest in stock market; ascertain what type of trading is preferred by the people who trade in stock market (intraday trading, swing trading, positional trading); to study the most purchased instruments in the market (equity shares, debentures, flexi blonds, mutual funds); to study the role of SEBI in regulating the stock market.

#### EXPERIENTIAL LEARNING

# 360 Huntington Fund, Boston, MA / Fund Analyst

Aug 2021 - Present

- Presented a pitch to buy a new stock; received majority voting from sector managers & other fund analysts and the order was
  executed.
- Researched & identified industry, sub industry, stock, impactful financial ratios, key drivers, financials and much more

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Trueblue India LLP, Haryana, India | Financial Analyst

Jan 2021 - April 2021

- Managed reviewing the final list of new drivers recruited by the TrueBlue U.S.A and adding them to various payroll portals like SAP,
   DHL, Tungsten for timely compensation. Modified the sequence of duties performed by analysts, enabling the drivers compensation reports to be prepared 3 days, 10% earlier, giving room for any last-minute changes.
- Delivered various reports and trackers like Cost Analysis Report, Time Sheet Report, Production Tracker, GBS Reports
- Resolved all onshore partners queries be it procedural issues or unique issues
- Was in charge of the new Centerline Department and was awarded for suggesting new functioning and **monetary changes** in the new department

# MTS Systema Smart Technologies, Haryana, India | Finance Intern

June 2019 - Aug 2019

- Completed the project "Studying and analyzing the financials of Mts Sistema Smart Technologies", where in I had to analyze the reduction in company's revenue due to its decline from 5 telecom circles to 3 telecom circles.
- Analyzed the financial statements, balance sheets & income statement of clients, created a priority list that needed consulting

# Bharti Airtel, Uttar Pradesh, India | Sales and Marketing Intern

June 2018 - Aug 2018

- Successfully accomplished the objectives of the internship, "Awareness and penetration of wire line products for Bharti Airtel in B2B segment", covered 97% of the target area, opening branch's access to 2 new technical parks.
- Closed deals with potential customers for co.'s Cellular data and Wi-Fi instruments, increasing branch's Wi-fi revenue by 4.3%.

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Bloomberg Market Concepts (BMC) Certification
- Financial Analysis course from Delhi Institute of Computer Courses
- Certified member for completing Technical Analysis Course with StockMentors- A National Stock Exchange registered broker